
{
  "questions": [
    {
      "no": "1",
      "question": "During the past 4 weeks, have you had any problems with your work or daily life due to your physical health?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Yes"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "No"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "B"
    },
    {
      "no": "2",
      "question": "During the past 4 weeks, have you had any problems with your work or daily life due to any emotional problems, such as feeling depressed, sad or anxious?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Yes"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "No"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "B"
    },
    {
      "no": "3",
      "question": "Overall how would you rate your mental health?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Excellent"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "Poor"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "A"
    },
    {
      "no": "4",
      "question": "Have you felt particularly low or down for more than 2 weeks in a row?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Very Often"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "Not At All"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "B"
    },
    {
      "no": "5",
      "question": "During the past two weeks, how often has your mental health affected your relationships? ",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Very Often"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "Not At All"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "B"
    },
    {
      "no": "6",
      "question": "Have you ever been diagnosed with a mental disorder before?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Yes"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "No"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "B"
    },
    {
      "no": "7",
      "question": "When did you last get your mental health examination done?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Between A Year Ago"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "More Than A Year Ago"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "A"
    },
    {
      "no": "8",
      "question": "Is there a history of mental disorder in your family?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Yes"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "No"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "B"
    },
    {
      "no": "9",
      "question": "Have you seen a therapist in the recent past?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Yes"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "No"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "A"
    },
    {
      "no": "10",
      "question": "Are you currently taking any medication?",
      "answers":[
        {"optionId": "A", "option": "Yes"},
        {"optionId": "B", "option": "No"}
      ],
      "correctOption": "A"
    }
  ]
}
